带球的那个 来自Dunbar
Him on the ball, from Dunbar.
县级两年制社区学院
现在正在读大专 但是...
He junior college now, but...
如果他成绩可以 就能去更好的学校(直升州立大学三年级)
he going to bigger places if he can make them grades.
他是咱们场上的法宝
He our edge, right there.
他打算去哪?
Where he going?
我不知道
I don't know.
马里兰大学队 乔治敦大学队
Terps, Hoyas,
密苏里大学队 堪萨斯大学队
Missouri, Kansas,
他们都想要这小子
they all want this cat.
好 咱们现在也有混合队了 你明白我在说什么吧
Okay, so we in the mix, too, now. You know what I'm talking about?
让臭Joe大吃一惊 他绝找不到像这样打球的人
Blow Proposition Joe's mind. He ain't got nobody balling like this.
他最好没有一个能这样打球的
He better not have one motherfucker balling like this.
我烦透了每年输给东边那些贱人
I'm tired of losing to these Eastside bitches every year.
都已经连续三年了 伙计
It's been three years running now, man.
它妈的都打得我没脾气了
Fucking with my morale, for real.
那个废柴怎么样了?
What happened to the faggot?
Omar?
那家伙消失了 哥们
That nigger in the winds, man.
你说消失是啥意思 伙计
What you mean he in the wind, man?
这城市有那么大吗?
This city ain't that big.
你知道那家伙窝起来时会干什么吗?
You know what that nigger do when he holed up somewhere?
他就打劫一两批货 在附近晃悠
He peel off one or two packages, roll around the neighborhood...
免费分发小包毒品
Giving away free vials and shit.
对 搞一些罗宾汉式的名堂
Yeah, on some real Robin Hood type shit.
如果咱们要追杀他
If we try and get at him...
就会听到不少家伙抱怨咱们坏他们的事
We going to have two dozen niggers saying that we on our way.
如果你想让我们动手 我们会去的
If you want us to hunt that nigger, we going to hunt.
不过我认为 明智之举是我们休战
But the smart play, I think, we call a truce...
把这事搁置片刻
Put this thing on hold for a hot second.
让那贱人放松了...
Let the faggot get comfortable...
到那时 咱们就爆他的头 崩 咱们摆平了他
And when he do, he'll pop up his head. Boom, we got him.
咱们等待的时候 混蛋们会说什么
What will motherfuckers be saying while we waiting?
人们看到那个挨千刀的贱人 公开露面时 会说什么
What people going to say when they see this cocksucking faggot out in the sunshine?
好像可以肆无忌惮的打劫我
Like it ain't no thing to take my shit.
小子跟我说得没两样吧
Kid's everything I said he was?
是啊 他很不错
Yeah, he is straight.
明年缺了他 我们都不知道咋办了
Don't know what we're going to do without him next year.
你怎么还没有签约
How come you ain't signed?
很多学校盯上我了
Lot of schools looking at me.
我在权衡
I'm listening.
不过 多个一万块也不赖 对吗
$10,000, though, that ain't bad, right?
是 很不错
No. It ain't.
一万给他 另加5千
10,000 for the kid,plus $5,000...
给这项目的捐款
Donation for the program.
成交
Done.
很好
Good.
给我从罚球线投30个 去吧
Give me 30 from the line and get out of here.
- 伙计 漂亮 小子 - 好吧 各位
- Yo, man, good job, baby. - All right, big guy.
我想 应该还有另外的5千...
And I assume there's another $5,000 right here,
因为我促成了这事?
For making this happen?
是啊 没免费的午餐 对吧
Ain't shit for free, right?
火线重案组 第一季 第九集 比赛日
The Wire S01E09 Game Day
* When you walk through the garden *
* You gotta watch your back *
* Well I beg your pardon *
* Walk the straight and narrow track *
* If you walk with Jesus *
* He's gonna save your soul *
* You gotta keep the devil *
* Way down in the hole *
* All the angels sing *
* About Jesus' mighty sword *
* And they'll shield you with their wings *
* And keep you close to the lord *
* Don't pay heed to temptation *
* For his hands are so cold *
* You gotta help me keep the devil *
* Way down in the hole *
"也许咱们赢了"  --Herc
那你靠什么赚钱
So, what you do for money?
没钱怎么过 对吧
Can't live without it, right?
你还在为那个打劫的小子难受 对吗
You still fucked up behind that stickup, man?
那算不到你头上
Shit ain't on you.
也算不到我头上
It ain't on me neither.
那混蛋抢了货仓 朝Sterling开枪
Motherfucker who robbed the stash shot Sterling.
他活该被收拾 无论你我做什么
He gonna get got no matter what you or me do.
我就是不想干了 我不想再干了
I just don't wanna play. I don't wanna play no more.
行吗
All right?
我在考虑去上学
I was thinking about going to school,
在Edmondson那边
Over at Edmondson...
问他们能否让我在期末回去
Ask if they'll let me back in at the end of the semester.
- 几年级 - 9年级(相当于初三)
- What grade? - Ninth.
9年级 靠 你多大了
Ninth? Shit, you how old?
16岁
Sixteen.
16岁? 伙计 你现在都该读11年级了(相当于高二)
Sixteen. Damn, man, you supposed to be a junior by now.
我听说 Stinkum被杀了
I heard Stinkum got killed.
是啊
Yeah.
靠
Damn.
- 我说过 我不想干了 - 我听到了
- I said I don't want to play. - I heard you.
- 我说过 我不想干 - 你也没事可干
-I said I don't want to play. - And you ain't got to do nothing.
我明白你的意思 拿去
I heard you. Take it.
快点 小子 别人在看
Hurry up, nigger, people looking.
你瞧 伙计 你这个聪明的小坏蛋
Look here, man, you a smart little motherfucker.
你回到Edmondson读书
You start back up at Edmondson...
你可能最后上哈佛之类的学校
You likely to finish up at Harvard or some shit like that.
相信吧 哥们
Believe, B.
你那里也有颗善良的心
And you got a good heart in there, too.
不像这里其他人
Not like the rest of these niggers.
- 喂 - Ronnie Mo在大楼区2号线
- Yeah? - Ronnie Mo on Tower Phone 2.
好
Right.
你他妈的在哪儿 你到底来不来拿这个
Where the fuck you at, man? You coming to get this shit or what?
冷静 我们在绕圈
Keep cool, we making rounds.
你知道 我不能像以前那样行动
You know I ain't moving like I used to.
好吧 一两个钟头 我们就到你那儿
All right, couple hours, we be at you.
好吧
All right.
Wee-Bey要去大楼收钱吗?
Wee-Bey picking up at the towers?
大概要个把小时
In a couple hours, give or take.
够咱们搞一次行动
Time enough for us to make a play.
Wallace怎么啦
What's up with Wallace?
没事
Nothing.
没事吗
Nothing?
没事
Nothing.
好着呐 随他去吧
It's all good, just leave him be.
该死
Damn.
靠
Fuck.
我真受够这里没电话用的滋味儿
I'm tired of not having a phone up in this joint.
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
好 好好溜达去吧
Yeah. Have a nice hike.
嗯
Yeah.
喂 你要订餐吗?
Hello, you make order?
你是谁
Who this?
- 你要订餐吗 好吃的菜汤 - 什么
- You make order? Good yakame. - What?
不送餐 你下单 你过来吃
Or no delivery. You make order, you come get.
好吃的菜汤 好面条
Good yakame, good noodle.
多送调料
Extra ketchup.
那到底啥玩意儿
What the fuck was that?
这是我那里的韩裔招待
That was my Korean counterman.
听着像华裔
Sounded Chinese.
你装得像他妈的能分清似的
Like you can fucking tell the difference.
这是给你们挑战的新领域 小伙子
It's a brave new world for you, boys.
- 12-14 - 12-14
12-14. 12-14.
- 请求和12-08通话 - 同意 14
- Request a lateral with 12-08. - Go ahead, 14.
08 你能换到3频道吗
08, can you go to Channel 3?
12-08 我收到
12-08, I got that.
- 你的位置 - McCullough与Preston路口
- Where you at? - McCullough above Preston.
我们正监视 平房区里的小子正在用的公共电话
We're on a good pay phone that the pit boys are now using.
我要到教堂上 盯紧了 伙计们
I'm up on the church. Hang close, boys.
也许能让你们活动活动筋骨
Might have a nice jack-up for you two.
难以置信 这些人还在干
I can't believe these boys still in business, man.
免费样品 样品马上到
Testers, testers coming in five.
新货啥样子 伙计
What's the new package, man?
黄盖 像炸弹一样带劲
Yellow tops. Shit is the bomb.
- 像炸弹一样带劲 - 瞧瞧那个
- Now shit is the bomb. - Check it.
那人过瘾的劲头胜过戒毒的劲
A man who wants to get high more than he wants to get clean.
那人的表现还不错的
He was doing good, too.
告诉你吧 那是胡扯 那些戒毒会面只是幌子
Told you, it was bullshit. Them meetings were just fronts.
那人好像很坚强 知道吗
The man sounded strong, you know?
随便吧
Whatever.
到时候咯
It's about that time.
- 糟糕 - 怎么了
- Shit. - What happened?
那是暴打我的小子
That's the boy who beat me down, man.
喂
Yo
这次来的货是黄盖 都很正 记住咯
The shits right here is yellow tops and they right so remember
你们觉得这个带劲 要告诉你们铁杆朋友
Where you caught this blast and tell your fiend-ass friends.
都排好队
Line the fuck up.
退开
Back up.
排好队 搞什么啊 排起队
Get in line, what the fuck? Line the fuck up.
都快滚开 该死 去你们的
Get the fuck out of here. Damn, fuck you all.
快来 这边
Hurry up. Over here.
捡到一个 过来 我捡到一个
Get one, girl, over here. I got one.
- 你捡到一个 - 我捡到一个
- You get one? - I get one.
站住
Hold up.
嘿 你捡到了吗
Hey, You catch one?
你瞧 你如果要 我有三个
You know, I got three if you need.
你那天在Samuel Morse的戒毒会上
You was at the meeting over at Samuel Morse.
一天先生 其实连那都算不上
Mr. One-Day Man. It wasn't even that.
但还是站出来了
Stood up, though.
既然你不要 为何过来拿免费样品
Why you down at the tester line if you ain't chasing?
试着让我外甥离开这里
Trying to get my little nephew off the corner.
他妈妈送他去Cumberland 知道吗
His mama sent him up to Cumberland, you know?
想让他在我祖母那里戒毒
Try to keep him clean at my grandma's.
他还远未堕落到谷底
He ain't anywhere near his bottom.
以后堕落到谷底 他才会明白
Got to see that bottom coming up at him.
也难啊 他还年轻 才24岁
Hard, too, 'cause he's young, 24.
多数人在35 40岁前 不会厌倦
Most people don't get tired till they're 35, 40.
你多大年纪了
How old are you?
心还年轻着呢
Young at heart.
Walon 伙计
Walon, man.
Bubs
Bubs.
让他们跑远点儿
Give them a long rope.
离公房区越远抓他 监听暴露的风险越小
The farther away from the projects you pop him, the less risk to the wire.
让监听见鬼去
Hell with the wire.
你说啥
Excuse me?
骗到你了 McNulty 你太好骗了
Gotcha, McNulty, you're too easy.
你们能从几种方式入手
You can come at this a few ways.
首先 我们需要所有皮包公司的名称
First thing is we need the names of all front companies...
有限合伙人 LLC 所有诸如此类的东西
Iimited partnerships, LLCs, and all that mess.
- LLC是啥 - 有限责任公司
- LLCs? - Limited liability corporations.
从Barksdale掌管的那个夜总会查起
Start with the nightclub which Barksdale owns.
查查Orlando 从地址入手
Look up Orlando's, by address,
你找到它 然后发现它归谁所有
You match it, and you see it's owned by who?
那是在Baltimore大街 对吗
It's on Baltimore Street, right?
找到了 是个业务经营企业(类似中国的个体户)
Got it. D & B enterprises.
把这交给Prez 让他屈尊
Give it to Prez, who's going to get off his ass
走到Preston大街的州办公大楼
And walk on over to the state office buildings on Preston Street.
Preston大街?
Preston Street?
毒品
公司登记办公室(工商局注册分局)
Corporate charter office.
公司什么
Corporate who?
钱
他们有每间公司在本州经商的
They have the paperwork on every corporation
档案和有限公司执照
And LLC licensed to do business in the state.
你在电脑里检索业务经营企业
You look up D & B Enterprises on the computer.
你将得到一小卷微缩胶片
You're going to get a little reel of microfilm.
同样调出公司注册文件
Pull the corporate charter papers that way...
记下你看到的每个名字
Write down every name you see.
公司负责人 股东 还有更重要的
Corporate officers, shareholders, or more importantly...
登记的常驻代表 通常是一名律师
The resident agent on the filing who is usually a lawyer.
当他们用个代表作为公司负责人
While they use front names, you know, as corporate officers...
他们通常让同一个律师做注册登记
They'll usually use the same lawyer to do the charter filing.
找到那个代表的名字 在电脑里检索
Find that agent's name, run it through the computer...
找到他代表登记的其他公司
Find out what other corporations he's done the filing for...
那样 我们就找到其他的皮包公司了
And that way we find other front companies.
他做那个的时候 我干什么
While he's doing that, what do I do?
你要埋头翻这本评估手册
You're gonna to keep your head in this assessment book.
寻找任何 你能联系到的Barksdale财产
Look up any properties that you can connect to Barksdale.
你咋知道那与Barksdale有关
How do you know it connects to Barksdale, right?
首先 你利用Prez从公司登记文档中
For one thing, you work off of what Prez gets you
为你找到的资料
From the corporate charter documents.
无论他发现的哪个 跟Barksdale有关的公司或个人
Whatever companies he links to Barksdale or people connected to him...
你就在本城的用地登记中 寻找那些公司
You look for those companies in the city land records.
举个例子
For example:
McNulty说 他听说Barksdale
McNulty said that he heard that Barksdale...
在Druid湖公园附近有栋公寓楼
Owned an apartment building up on Druid Park Lake.
你就在Reservoir Hill的所有街区找
You look up all the blocks on Reservoir Hill.
看是否有任何 由业务经营企业拥有的物业
See if there's anything owned by D & B Enterprises...
或者Prez在公司登记档案中
Or any other company that Prez finds...
找到的任何公司 或者其他类似的
Through corporate charter or anything similar.
如果你找到相符的资料 你就记下土地登记号
If you find something that fits, you write down the folio number...
那么 你稍后就能在政府大楼里查询它
So that you can look it up later at the courthouse.
你如果没找到
You don't find anything...
就记下在湖边拥有多单元房产的
Just take the names of all the corporate listings
所有的公司名称
For the multi-units near the lake.
你把那清单告诉Prez 他会调出相应的登记档案
You call that list over to Prez, who pulls the charter papers...
然后他会寻找关联
And he'll look for connections.
这就像寻宝游戏
It's like a scavenger hunt.
可是 如果Barksdale很谨慎呢
But what if Barksdale is careful?
我是指 如果我们在任何东西上 都找不到他的名字呢
I mean, what if we can't find his name on anything?
在这个国家里
In this country...
某个人的名字肯定要登记在纸上
Somebody's name has got to be on a piece of paper.
一个堂兄弟 女朋友 祖母 一个他能信任的警官
A cousin, a girlfriend, a grandmother, a lieutenant he can trust...
某个人的名字就登记在纸上
Somebody's name is on a piece of paper.
而棘手之处在于
And here's the rub:
你追查毒品
You follow drugs...
你能查到吸毒者和毒贩子
You get drug addicts and drug dealers.
可是你开始追踪钱
But you start to follow the money...
你就不知道 到底会查到谁头上了
And you don't know where the fuck it's going to take you.
我们进行这个的时候
While we're running around on this,
你要去做什么
What are you going to do?
巴尔的摩市
选举委员会
你需要什么吗
You need something?
对 请给我
Yeah. Let me get the...
西区的竞选财务报告
Campaign financial reports for the western districts...
事实上 所有市级的选举
And actually, any citywide race.
你需要每季报告 还是独立捐款者清单
You want quarterly reports or individual donor lists?
都要 劳驾
Both, please.
那可有好几百页
It'll be a couple hundred pages.
真的吗 我全都要了
Really? I'll take all of it.
靠 咋回事
What the fuck, man?
司机 用你的右手伸到窗口 打开车门
Driver, with your right hand, reach for the window, open the door.
快 赶紧
Come on, hurry up, man.
下车
Step out of the car.
丢掉拐杖 扔掉拐杖
Drop the cane, toss the cane.
转过身去
Come around to the back.
好吧
All right.
转身
Turn around.
先生 车里面有什么东西 需要申报给我们吗
Sir, is there anything in the vehicle we should know about?
没有
Nope.
没枪 没毒品吗
No guns, drugs?
我啥都没有
Me ain't got shit.
眼前这笔钱 难道不是我从你车里找到的?
This money right here, I didn't just pull this out of your truck?
什么钱
What money?
靠 这笔破钱我们得数上一天了
Damn, we'll be counting this limp-dick cash all day.
你们拿着这些要去哪里
Where you guys going with all this?
像他说的 那不是我们的
Like the man said, it ain't ours.
这不是你们的?
It ain't yours?
那么 我们要是拿走了 你们不介意吗
So, you don't mind if we just take it off your hands?
随你们便
Do what you feel.
你们假装从这车上找到了钱
You pretending to take money out this truck.
我根本不知道它在里面
I didn't even know it was there.
你瞧 我知道这是咋回事
You know, I know how that shit is.
有一天 我从我的沙发取沙发垫
The other day, I took up the sofa cushions off my couch...
出乎我意料 找到1.4美元
Found $1 .40 I didn't even know was there.
你们没的告我 对吧?
You all ain't got no charge, right?
对 混蛋 我们没有罪名
No, fucker, we do not have a charge.
我们只拿走你的钱
We just got your money.
你想要回去 你得跟
You want it back, you can explain it
州检察官解释 你从哪里弄来的
To the state's attorney where you got it.
祝你们今天顺利 听到没
You all enjoy your day now, you hear?
* 当我早晨醒来 从我床上下来 *
As I wake up in the morning And get out of my bed...
给我三支
Give me three.
* 当我早上醒来 从我床上下来 *
* As I wake up in the morning And get out of my bed *
* 想起儿时伙伴 早已如土 *
* I'm thinking about the people I grew up with long dead *
* 一起长大的兄弟 锒铛入狱 *
* The brothers I grew up with locked up *
* 我在脑海中随性发挥 *
* I'm freestyling off the top of my head *
* 你知道 这不赖*
* You know, it's swell *
* Patti LaBelle 我喜欢她 可是Regina Bell 更喜欢*
* Patti LaBelle I like her But Regina Bell is better *
王八蛋
Motherfucker!
王八蛋 想偷我们货
Motherfucker, trying to steal our shit.
王八蛋
Motherfucker!
- 钓到你的希望了 Bubbs? - 是啊
- Fished your wish, Bubbs? - Yeah.
是啊
Yeah.
你该瞧瞧他们抓住的那个
And you should've seen the one that got away.
知道吗 我差点就被逮到了
I nearly got killed behind this caper, you know?
这就是江湖 Bubbs
It's all in the game, Bubbs.
是吗
Yeah?
喂 Bubb
Yo, Bub...
这不给劲
This ain't shit.
我也没过瘾
I'm not high, neither.
这是Arm & Hammer(食用碱品牌)
It's fucking Arm & Hammer.
咱们刚吸了碱面
We just been firing baking soda.
没关系 伙计 我会再想个计划
It's all right, man. I'll just come up with another plan.
我干过一次 不是吗?
I did it once, right?
我靠
Fuck me.
闭嘴
???
Carv 你去一个餐厅
Carv, you go to a restaurant...
假如女侍者给你优质体面的服务
And say the waitress gives you good, decent service.
- 你要给多少小费 - 我给多少小费
- How much do you tip? - How much do I tip?
优良的服务
For good service.
我不清楚 15%吧
I don't know, 15%.
有些人给20%小费
Some people tip 20%.
有些人很有钱
Some people got money.
你认为 Wee-Bey会给多少小费
What you think Wee-Bey would tip?
如果那里没有被监听 你就算个聪明的家伙了
You'd be a clever motherfucker if there wasn't a wiretap running.
你什么意思
What do you mean?
比如咱们上交2万美元
Say we turn in $20,000,
而今下午 领导们听那监听录音
And this afternoon, the bosses are listening to the wiretap...
他们听到 咱们从车里拿出3万美元
And they hear we took $30,000 out of that car.
你没想到那点 对吗
Didn't think of that, did you?
我们在市中心西边找到不少物业
We're finding a lot of stuff on the west side of downtown..
可能是他的 就在Howard街边
That might be his, over by that Howard Street corridor.
什么样的物业
What kind of property?
廉价商铺
Low-rent commercials.
很多空置的
A lot of vacants.
Avon Barksdale要一片 空置商铺干什么用
The fuck does Avon Barksdale want with a string of empty storefronts?
这样太草率
This feels premature.
- 哪样 - 追踪资产
- What does? - Chasing up assets.
我们连告这个人的一个罪名都没找到
We're not close to putting a charge to the man.
应该先考虑那个
That should be the priority.
咱们对Avon Barksdale提出指控
We put a charge to Avon Barksdale...
副局就会叫停咱们 让咱们回家啦
The Deputy shuts us down, tells us to go home.
你想要本案的金钱走向 机不可失 时不再来 队长
You want the money side of this case, it's now or never, Lieutenant.
我在这儿干活呐
I'm working here.
- 大概有两三万美元 - 点心钱
- Maybe $20,000 or $30,000. - Dollars for donuts.
你们该瞧瞧他们的表情
You should've seen the looks on their faces.
Wee-Bey说什么
What did Wee-Bey say?
"什么钱"
"What money?"
剩下的唯一苦差事 就是坐在这里清点
The only hassle is we need to sit here and count this shit.
做证物登记
Do the ECU Submissions.
这都是些零碎的小钞
And it's all limp-dick, dime-vial money.
刚从街头收到的脏票子
Dirty bills right off the corner.
你们都看到平房小子们 在新公共电话那里 对吗
You all got the pit boys on a fresh pay phone, right?
是的 在McCullough
Yeah, on McCullough.
- 你们拍了照片吗 - 噢 是的
- You take pictures? - oh yeah.
很好 咱们肯定要给那个电话 加一份书面申请
Good, we're gonna need an additional affidavit to get up on that phone.
再加30天吗 McNulty?
Another 30 days, McNulty?
我他妈的到底干啥了
What the fuck did I do?
头天他争取 第二天他就准备放弃了
One day he fights, the next day he's ready to roll over.
他到底要不要这案子了
Does he want this fucking case or not?
让他喘口气吧 Jimmy
Give him some slack, Jimmy.
他还在挣扎怎么处理这案子呢
He's wrestling with the angels on this one.
我的幸运笔呢?
Where's my lucky pen?
- 你准备好了吗 婊子 - 对 我好了
- You ready, bitch? - Yeah, I'm ready.
我想爬到你膝盖上 像吃大棒棒糖那样吸吮你
I wanna get on my knees and suck you like a great big lollipop.
好耶 吸吧
Yeah, suck it.
好 我明白那是你最喜欢的
Yeah, I know that's your favorite.
让我这样舔 你喜欢吗
Let me lick that. You like that?
你喜欢吗
You like that?
我想让你从后面操我
I want you to butt-fuck me.
当内容无关时 我们应该关闭监听
We're supposed to turn off the tap when it's non-pertinent.
靠 不行 这太棒了
Fuck, no, this is too good.
- 我操 - 老爹 好耶
- Fuck me. - Daddy, yeah.
我绝对不会做这次笔录
There's no way I'm transcribing this stuff.
抚摸你自己
Touch yourself.
行
Yeah.
- 我的B现在湿透了 - 性爱电话
- My pussy is so wet right now. - Phone sex?
笑死我了
Shit was hilarious.
你明白 如果内容无关 你们应该在90秒后关闭的
You're supposed to shut down after 90 seconds if it's non-pertinent.
你肯定像个溜光的甜甜圈 你明白吗
You're gonna to look like a glazed donut, you know that?
是那样吗
Is that right?
我要过去 把你的三个洞都干了
I'm gonna get there and fuck you in all three holes.
- 那你要路过这里吗 - 明天 对
- So, you're gonna come past here? - Tomorrow, yeah.
不过 我今晚要去Argyle街一趟
But I need to go past Argyle Street tonight.
- 看看Wallace - Wallace
- Check in with Wallace. - Wallace?
自从我们帮大楼里的伙计 抓住那个打劫小子 他就不干了
He's off the hook since we helped the tower crew get that stickup boy.
我告诉你吧 Wallace很烦
I'm telling you, Wallace is bugging.
几乎都没从房间里出来过
Don't hardly even come out of that room no more.
- 他为啥那样 - 我想 他也许在过毒瘾
- Why he be like that? - I think he might be getting high.
- Wallace? - 那小子这样可吓着我了
- Wallace? - Boy scaring me with his shit.
- 好吧 你晚点儿在传呼我吧 - 那就行
- All right, you holler at me later. - That'll work.
现在有关了 对吗
Pertinent now, right?
你如果能解释 为何自慰10分钟以后 咱们还在监听那线路
If you can explain why we're still on the line after 10 minutes jerking off.
你得有理有据
You got to justify that.
三个洞可能代表三个窝点
Maybe three holes was the code for three stash houses.
Omar
Omar.
Omar来了
Omar coming.
你们听到吗 我说Omar来了
Did you hear me? I said Omar coming.
- 赶快离开吧 - Omar来了
- Let's get out of here. - Omar coming.
我说啊 Omar过来了
I said, Omar coming through.
有人要麻烦了 来吧 咱们走
Somebody in trouble now. Come on, let's go.
在我大动干戈以前 你们还是把门打开吧
You all need to open this door, man, before I huff and puff.
这两句源于童话"三只小猪"
快点儿 马上 不要和我罗嗦 不要废话
Come on, now, by the hairs of your chinny-chin-chin.
Omar 你最好走开 我们这儿有MAC-10(枪)
Omar, you best roll out, we up in here with a MAC-10.
我可不觉得 Terrell 我可不觉得
I thinks not, Terrell, I thinks not.
你们都放明白点儿 别浪费我的时间
You all might need to think this through and stop wasting my time.
因为Omar明天会来
Because Omar can come back tomorrow.
还有后天
And the next day.
还有大后天
我会从后面给你们一人一颗子弹
And I will put a bullet in all you all behind,
要是你们还是这样 听见没?
What happen right now, you heard?
这还差不多
Fair enough.
给你 不用找了
Here you go, keep it.
你打算怎么演这出儿
How do you wanna play it?
穷追猛打 让她别无选择
Hard and tight, like she's got no choice.
- Shardene Ennis - 小姐 咱们得谈谈
- Shardene Ennis. - Miss, we need to talk.
谈什么
About what?
得进去谈
It's a downtown talk.
这边走 来吧
This way. Come on.
给我一份2加2
Give me a two and two.
- 干什么 - 你有什么
- What's up? - What you got?
土产的 2元1支 你要吗?
Family affair, two-for-one, you up?
- 不 我不要 - 好吧
- No. Not me. - All right.
你认为 这些小卵石怎么到楼顶上的
How you figure these little pebbles get up on top of the roof?
大家都到哪儿去了
Where's everybody at?
也许这事都结束了 没人劳神告诉咱们一声
Maybe the whole thing is over and no one bothered to tell us.
也许咱们赢了
Maybe we won.
情况不对头
Something ain't right.
来吧 咱们去转转
Come on, let's take a ride.
- 我喜欢这些 - 是吗
- I like these. - yeah?
这玩具家具真棒
The toy furniture is great.
玩具屋缩微物品
Doll house miniatures.
这是个爱好
It's a hobby.
我们年轻时 我姐姐有个玩具屋 不过
My sister had a dollhouse when we were young, but...
没有像这么精致的 我可以吗
Nothing as nice as these. Can l?
当然
Sure, babe.
那是胡桃木大理石顶浴室橱
That's a walnut marble-top vanity.
19世纪晚期 新文艺复兴风格
Renaissance revival, late 19th century.
你有房间摆放它们吗
Do you have a house for them?
没有 我只是做出来卖掉
No, I just make them and sell them.
那可有点悲哀
That seems kind of sad.
你该给它们个房间
You should have a house for them.
咱们可以用队长的办公室
We can use the Lieutenant's office.
不行
No.
我什么也不要
I ain't asked for nothing.
怎么样 Tasha 你长得太漂亮了 姑娘
What's up, Tasha? You got too pretty, girl.
进屋去 Tash
Go inside, Tash.
我在考虑戒掉
I'm thinking about getting clean.
再一次
Again.
我在想 你知道 我无处可去 也许
I was thinking, you know, I ain't got no other place to go, maybe....
找错地方了 对吧
That's wrong, right?
这不对 是吗 对不起
That ain't right, right? Sorry.
对不起
I'm sorry.
等等
Wait.
只能走后门
Back door only.
地下室有个旧沙发
There's an old sofa in the basement
我会给你留些毯子
And I'll throw you down some blankets.
你要敢走上楼梯 我就把你交给警察
You try to come up those stairs, and I'm gonna call the police on you.
我保证一定会
I swear I will.
西Baltimore的都去度假了啊
West fucking Baltimore is on vacation.
没有人在平房区 高楼区闲逛
No crews slinging in the low-rises, the towers.
他妈的怎么回事
What the fuck?
- 谁跟谁比赛 - 西区对东区
- Who's playing who? - West against East.
- Baltimore? - 公房区 伙计
- Baltimore? - The projects, man.
公房区的"角斗大赛"
The bragging rights to the projects.
公房区还有球队?
The projects got a ball team?
你在Orlando吧工作多久了
How long you been working at Orlando's?
- 四五个月 - 你喜欢吗
- Four, five months. - You like it?
交房租而已
Pays the rent.
我想你在那儿肯定看到很多
You must see a lot there, I imagine.
你是什么意思
What do you mean?
那里有很多玩家 有很多把戏在上演
There's a lot of players there. A lot of game being played.
我对那一无所知 我只为小费工作
I know nothing about that, I just work for tips.
- 只为小费 - 小费 酒水
- For tips? - Tips, drinks.
你明白 我是个大姑娘了
You know, I'm just a b-girl.
我不做非分的事
I don't mess with nothing beyond that.
那里有些姑娘
Some of the girls in there,
她们或多或少喜欢毒品
They're into drugs and whatnot.
有些姑娘在楼上开房做爱 但...
And some of them turn tricks in the rooms upstairs but...
我基本就呆在吧台
I mostly just stay at the bar.
Ennis小姐 我们不对人做指控
Miss Ennis, it's rare when we ask somebody
就带他们到局里 这种情况很少见
To come on downtown with us and we don't have a charge on them.
我们不告诉他们 我们准备谈什么
We don't tell them what we're gonna talk about.
他们也毫不抱怨地跟着来
And they come along without complaining.
这几乎没见过
That hardly ever happens.
少见 从未见过
Rarely, if ever.
我以为你们有理由
I figure you got your reasons.
掌握Orlando吧的那伙人
The crew that runs Orlando's...
他们去年杀了大约12个人
They've dropped about a dozen bodies over the last year.
他们在每个公房区行销售毒品
And they're running the drugs in every housing project...
就在马丁.路德.金大道以西
West of the Martin Luther King.
我对此一无所知 我为小费而工作
I don't know anything about that. I just work for tips.
可你现在知道了 因为我们正告诉你
But now you do know, because we're telling you.
你认识一个叫Keisha Michaels的姑娘吗
You know a girl named Keisha Michaels?
她跟我一起跳舞
She dances with me.
她怎么样
How's she doing?
我估计 还好吧
All right, I guess.
请允许我们失陪一会儿
Will you excuse us a moment?
那么 你怎么看
So, what do you think?
我认为 她是个可爱的人
I think she's a sweetheart.
我认为 如果我们施点压 她会醒悟
I think if we push her hard, she'll tumble.
你想给她看那照片吗
You want to show her the pictures?
我想做得更好
I want to do better than that.
加油 伙计 防守战术
Come on, man, play defense.
- 快啊 - 防守
- Let's go! - "D" up, B.
他是谁
Who is he?
那是Marcus Rivera 伙计
That's Marcus Rivera, right there, man.
他来自克利夫顿湖 那家伙在意大利打球
He out of Lake Clifton. That nigger played in ltaly and shit.
哥们
Slim.
咋回事 伙计
What's up, man?
你要跑到欧洲那么远 去找一个投手吗
You got to go all the way to Europe to get you a ringer?
不 他现在回家了
No, he home now.
不过 我看到你 从大专学校拉人来
But I see you pulling boys out the junior colleges.
他是东区的 去了Dunbar而已
He from Eastside, went to Dunbar.
咋回事 浪荡哥 你怎么会穿身西装
What's up, playboy? How come you wearing that suit?
说真的 现在有30多度(华氏85度)
For real, it's 85 fucking degrees out here
你想学Pat Riley嘛(NBA著名教练)
And you trying to be like Pat Riley.
穿着正经 做事投入 狗娘养的
Look the part, be the part, motherfucker.
你他妈的拿个假笔记板到处晃悠
You walking around with a fake fucking clipboard.
你连比赛计划都看不懂 面对现实吧
You can't even read a playbook. Be for real.
一群贱人
Bunch of bitches.
耶
Yeah.
加油
Let's go.
真不赖
That was nice.
那小子如有神助 是吧
That boy was talking to God, right?
你们不是该上班吗
Ain't you all on the clock?
你们不是吗
Ain't you?
我们在休息
We on break.
那我们也在休息
Then we on a break, too.
这比赛有啥名堂
What's up with this game?
我们每年都办 你知道吗
Just something we do every year, you know?
东边大战西边
Eastside versus Westside niggers.
输方下周要在Druid山举办个大派对
Loser got to throw a big-ass party at Druid Hill next weekend.
谁占优啊
Who's favored?
过去两年东边赢了
Eastside won the last two years.
我的天
My boys.
周一早上被发现
Found nude Monday morning,
裸体 被藏在Reisterstown路边 一个垃圾箱里
In a Dumpster off Reisterstown road,
靠近北边
Above Northern.
化验结果 海洛因和可卡因阳性
Toxicology is positive for heroin and cocaine.
在一个垃圾箱里?
In a Dumpster?
用一块地毯卷着
Rolled up in a rug.
她吸毒过量 而跟他一起的人啥也没做...
She overdosed and whoever was with her didn't do shit...
只是把她卷起来 丢了
But roll her up and throw her away.
因为这就是他们的作为
Because that's how they do.
在阴道 肛门和口腔里检出精液
Positive for semen in vaginal, anal and oral cavities.
所有的腔体各有三种血型
Three different blood types, all secretors.
他们跟她性交 然后弃尸
They fucked her and threw her away.
我们之所以能认出她是谁
The only reason we knew who she was,
还有她想要做什么
Or what she was about...
还有对像你这样的人 她意味着什么...
Or what she might mean to someone like you...
都是因为 我们一直在监视...
Is because we've been keeping an eye on the people
掌控Orlando吧的人
Who run Orlando's for some time now.
我们设法了解他们在讲什么
We got ways of knowing what they're saying...
他们在考虑什么
What they're thinking.
你知道 他们怎么描述这位吗
You know what they said about this one?
那个蠢婊子不知道 Little Man的派对上的毒品有多正
That the stupid bitch didn't know how good the snort was at Little Man's party.
那是她自己的错 这就是他们的所作所为
That it was her own fault. That's how they do it.
他们利用别人 等他们抛弃别人时
They use people, and when they throw them away...
他们就托辞说 这跟他们无关
They find a way to say it ain't on them.
扯谎的王八蛋
Lying motherfucker.
他说过 他们送她去了医院
He said they took her to a hospital.
现在 回去防守
Now, get back on "D."
瞧瞧Avon 他乐坏了
Check out Avon. He's freaking.
靠 老天 我们得赢下这场
Shit, man, we got to win this one.
我认为Avon在这里
I think Avon's here.
哪里
Where?
好像我知道他长啥样似的
Like I know what he looks like?
一个黑人 支持西区的吧
He's a black guy rooting for Westside.
我们可能看到Avon本人
We might have a visual on Avon.
在Cloverdale的街头球赛中
Street ball game up at Cloverdale.
Greggs和Freamon去哪里了
Where's Greggs and Freamon?
他们在对带来的那个舞女施压
Pressing the stripper they picked up.
你和Carver让对讲机开着
You and Carver stay on the radio.
- 我们该跟踪他 - 为啥?
- We should follow him. - Why?
他不会在你能看到他的地方 接触毒品或钱 队长
He ain't gonna touch drugs or money anywhere you can see him, Lieutenant.
在缉毒科 我们跟踪嫌犯
In Narcotics we follow guys.
我们做得不错 我们借此立案
We do it well, we make cases on it.
上路
Mount up.
咱们盯这家伙三个月了
We been on this guy three months.
你就不想看他一眼吗
Don't you even want to get a look at him?
如果我在街上遇到Avon Barksdale 我也认不出他来
I wouldn't know Avon Barksdale if I fell over him in the street.
关键是 我没有必要
The thing is, I don't need to.
我们可以凭声音证据抓到他 其他都没戏
We get him by voice alone or we don't get him.
耶 宝贝
Yeah, baby!
主队比客队
33:45
中场休息
Half-time.
你给自己找了个好投手
You got yourself a fine ringer.
是啊 今年你要栽 你明白我在说什么吗
Well, yeah, baby,it's not your year, you know what I'm talking about?
表面如此 不过你永远不确定
It look that way, but you never know.
我确定 伙计 我们领先12分
I know, man, we up 1 2.
是的 你们领先 不过
Yeah, you is, but...
Joe的口头禅 也是他的外号Proposition Joe
我有个提议给你们
I got a proposition for you.
好
Okay.
翻倍如何
Double down?
咱们把赌注干脆加到六位数
Let's give this wager a clean six figures.
你当真吗 我不在乎 那是你的钱
You serious? I don't give a fuck. It's your money.
你愿意你就浪费吧 你明白我的意思吧?
You can waste it if you want, you know what I'm talking about?
有人看见他吗
Anyone got him?
- 64-C呼叫总部 - 12-10
- 64-Charlie to central K. - 12-10.
12-10
12-10.
你们发现他了吗?
You have him?
队长 我都不知道自己在找什么
Lieutenant, I don't even know what I'm looking for.
目标已确认 位于边线 穿红衬衫 白色遮阳帽
Got him marked. On the sideline, red shirt, white visor.
我看他是教练之类的吧
I think he's coaching or something.
这该死的小个子是谁
Who this fucking midget?
防住那个小个子 伙计
Get that midget out of here, B.
- 你为什么呼我 - 伙计 我们手头紧了
- Why you holler at me? - Man, we getting down to it.
时候到了会来找你们
I get to you when I get to you.
就是那里 那个就是窝点
That's it, we're on the stash.
- 是吗 - 嗯哼
- We are? - mm-hmm.
Sydnor不在楼顶的时候 你怎么能写下他的名字
How can you put that down when Sydnor wasn't on the roof?
是 他在那里
Yes, he was.
不 他不在 他跟Daniels在一起
No, he's not, he's with Daniels.
不 他没跟去
No, he isn't.
主队比客队 75:77
他妈的给老子让开
Get the fuck out of here.
裁判 这咋回事
Ref, what the fuck?
他妈的咋回事
What the fuck?
咋回事 裁判 咋回事
Yo, ref, yo, ref, what the fuck?
那小子犯规了 明显 清清楚楚的
The boy was fouled. Clear, straight up!
你怎么能不吹那个
How you going to not call that?
你如果需要 我能把时间吹回去 重新比赛
If you want, I can put time back on the clock and replay it.
你在提议重赛吗
You talking about a do-over?
提议要重赛吗 这比赛不是那么打的
Talking about a fucking do-over? That's not how the game is played!
你不能那么做
You can't do that!
难以置信 这家伙居然说要重来一次
Believe this shit? Nigger talking about doing it again.
我不想惹麻烦 行吗
I don't want any trouble, okay?
不比就没麻烦了
Ain't going to be no trouble over no ball.
伙计 你是裁判 对吧
Man, you supposed to be the ref, right?
你为什么不坚持你立场?
Why don't you stand up for your fucking self?
你这个娘们
You pussy.
你不能让任何混蛋在你头上撒野
You can't let any old motherfucking nigger get in your face,
你明白吗
You understand?
现在 滚
Now, walk away.
走开 转身 他妈的滚得远远的
Walk away. Turn around and walk the fuck away.
无知的蠢货
Ignorant motherfucker.
- 咱们没事吧 - 对 咱们没事 宝贝
- We cool? - Yeah, we cool, baby.
你告诉你们的人 周六中午到这公园里
You tell your people to come to the park, Saturday at noon.
当然 你要是再到西边来 没有篮球在手上
Of course you come on the Westside again, without a ball...
我就点你的天灯
I'm gonna light your ass up.
D'Angelo
D'Angelo?
你认识他?
You know him?
此时此刻 算是认识吧
At this point, it feels like I do.
我们算是同居了
We sort of moved in together.
他似乎与众不同
He seemed like he was different.
我得离开那个夜总会
I have to quit the club.
是 你应该 可是不是现在
Yes, you do. But not just yet.
我们需要你的协助
We need your help.
这就是我们找你的原因
Which is why we came to you.
- 我不知道别的 - Keisha不是第一个
- I don't know what else-- - Keisha was not the first.
除非有人勇敢一点儿站出来
Unless somebody steps up a little bit,
否则 她也不会是最后一个
She's not going to be the last neither.
你喜欢那个吗
You like that one?
不如你留着它吧
Why don't you keep it?
谢谢
Thank you.
他上了一辆福特Excursion SUV
He's getting into a black Ford Excursion.
收到
Copy that.
他开出来了 朝Collington路北侧
He's pulling out, north on Collington.
11-71
11-71.
你从北边平行跟踪 我从南边跟他
You got the parallel on the north, I got him on the south.
11-71 我看到他 他似乎想朝Oliver以东去
11-71, I got him. Looks like he's going east on Oliver.
他刚停下
He just parked.
Oliver东侧
East of Oliver.
12-10 你在视线内跟踪
12-10, you keep the eyeball.
11-71 你到Federal占位
11-71, take up a position on Federal,
西Montford
West of Montford.
我从南边跟过来
I'm coming up from the south.
11-71 我收到
11-71, I copy that.
他只是停在那里
He's just sitting there.
- 他在掉头返回 - 收到
- He's doubling back. - Copy.
他向南去了Montford路
He's south on Montford.
他在Preston和Milton路口闯过红灯 目前在Milton路南侧
He jumped the light at Preston and Milton and is south on Milton.
确认他没有开到Chase路
Be advised that he didn't make it to Chase.
11-71 你们的情况
11-71, what's your status?
他不可能溜过我们这里
He couldn't have gone past us.
11-71 这边没有情况
11-71, nothing on this side.
肯定是藏起来了
Must have went to ground.
好吧 你们原地待命 我过去看看
All right, hold your positions. I'll take a look.
他又打电话了 同一部公用电话
He called again, same pay phone.
嗓音一样吗
Same voice?
那是主窝点 肯定是的 行动规律都符合
It was the main stash house, it's got to be. The pattern fits.
公屋区是谁接的电话
Who took the call at the projects?
谁知道 楼顶上又没人
Who knows. There was no one on the roof.
Sydnor跟着Daniels 上街跟踪Avon去了
Sydnor was off with Daniels, chasing Avon in the street.
我们今天也走运
We had a good day, too.
Kima说服了Avon酒吧里一个舞女
Kima turned one of the dancers over at Avon's club.
那个跟D'Angelo上床的
The one who's fucking D'Angelo.
这家伙很厉害
This guy's good.
我们对他什么方法都用了
We threw everything we had at him.
你知道他们怎么说 愚蠢的罪犯培养愚蠢的警察
You know what they say, stupid criminals make stupid cops.
我很自豪能追捕这个家伙
I'm proud to be chasing this guy.
目前我们发现四个皮包公司 经营各种业务
We got four front companies so far, buying up all kinds of shit.
一个酒吧 一栋公寓楼 一家殡仪馆
A club, an apartment building, a funeral home...
还有市中心西边Howard街走廊的很多房产
And a lot of real estate on the west side of downtown by the Howard Street corridor.
都是商铺和仓库
Shop fronts and warehouses.
都在Barksdale的名下吗?
Barksdale's name on it?
多数是挂名的 有些是在亲戚下面
Fronts, mostly. Relatives, some.
我可以坐下吗?
Mind if I have a seat?
关键是 他控制那些公房区已经有一年多 而那是个财源
He's had the projects for more than a year and it's a money factory.
我们截获Wee-Bey那天 有2万2千美元
We popped Wee-Bey coming out the other day with $22,000.
那些小子在电话上说 那不算大损失
The boys talking on the wire were saying it wasn't much of a loss.
2万2千美元
$22,000?
那只是大楼和平房区一个上午的收益
That's just from one morning from the towers and the pit.
加上街头的 那大概接近3万美元
Add the avenue corners, you're probably up near $30,000.
再加晚上的收益 到6万
Another take for the evening, $60,000.
一天?
A day?
保守算 那就是一年2千5百万
That's $25 million a year, conservatively.
你刨去20%的运营开支和损失
You take out 20% for running expenses and spillage...
你还是能每月净赚一百万
And you are still clearing $1 million a month.
那么 这钱都到哪儿去了
So, where's it all go?
他没露一点儿痕迹
He shows no flash.
他没有房子 他名下没汽车
He's got no house, no car in his name...
没珠宝 没服装
No jewelry, no clothes.
只有那些皮包公司和物业
Just front companies and the property.
还有政治捐献
And political contributions.
仅上个月就有7万5千
$75,000 the last month alone...
全部来自他的皮包公司 或者公司的负责人
All from his front companies or their listed officers.
这还只是匆匆一瞥
And that's just at a quick glance.
我只合计了合法的捐款
I'm just totaling up the legal contributions.
你逮到过Damien Price那样的 州参议员的助手
You've got the likes of Damien Price, aide to a state senator...
只要他需要 随时能从公屋区 开车带走2万美元现金
Driving out $20,000 in cash from the projects whenever he feels it.
我明白你不想听到这个 队长
I know you don't want to hear this, Lieutenant...
可是钱是真格的 而且无处不在了
But the money is real and it's everywhere.
比毒品更严重 钱才是至关重要的
And more than the drugs, it's the money that matters.
我没跟别人上床 如果这就是你在想的
I ain't fucked nobody else if that's what you thinking.
好吧 我说 去它的 你如果要走 那就走吧
All right, I mean, fuck it. If you want to go, then go!
可是 他妈的你可以给我个理由
But you could give me a goddamn reason.
对你来说 我是什么人
What do I look like to you?
你什么意思
What you mean?
对你来说 我是什么人
What do I look like to you?
你是个姑娘 一个女人
You look like a girl, a woman...
漂亮女人 你很好 咋了
A beautiful woman, you're fine, what?
对你来说 我不是垃圾吗?
I don't look like trash to you?
宝贝 这跟你的工作无关
Baby, this ain't about what you do.
我不像那种 你能用地毯卷起来
I don't look like something you could roll up in a rug...
扔进垃圾桶的东西吗
And throw in the trash?
Shardene
Shardene.
队长 你呼我们? 我们都快到家了
Lieutenant, you paged us? We were almost home.
坐下
Sit.
- 喂 再查一下我的账 - 有多糟
- Yeah? Checked my count again, yo. - How bad?
不太糟 伙计
Not too bad, man.
- 我们被截了2万2 - 2万2 就那么多?
- We got hit about $22,000. - $22,000? That's all?
好吧
All right.
我拿到二号 三号 五号和六号大楼的
I got towers two, three, five and six...
另一捆贴"P"字 代表平房区
And another one labeled "P" for the pit.
一号和四号的在哪里
Where's one and four?
电话监听中 我们截获他们2万2
It's on the wire that we took them for $22,000.
你们两个猪头上交1万5 其余的在哪儿
You shitheads turned in $15,000. Where's the rest?
队长 我们没有...
Lieutenant, we ain't got--
你们在明天上班报道前...
You have till roll call tomorrow...
都可以去你们藏的地方找一找
To crawl back to whatever rock you hid it under.
拿回来之后交到物证科
It comes back and it goes to ECU.
那就当没有发生过
This doesn't happen.
别跟我来这套 别在我的队伍里
Not with me. Not with my unit.
我要是偷了 不会不告诉你的
I wouldn't steal and not tell you about it.
这是Avon的货
This some of Avon's shit.
你让Avon Barksdale满城追杀你
You got Avon Barksdale chasing your ass all around town...
你还有时间劫他的货?
And you still find time to take his shit.
现在 它们是你的了
It's your shit now.
我要这个干嘛
What I want with that?
大家会想要来干嘛?
What anybody want with that, man?
你开多少价?
How much you asking?
免费
We free.
免费?
Free?
我要说 我有个小提议给你
I'm saying, I got a little proposition for you.
提议就是 你免费得到4千块的货
Proposition is, you get four G-packs for free...
你给我个找到Avon的方法
You give me some better idea on how I can reach Avon.
怎么联系他?
How to contact him?
你们刚比过一场球赛 不是吗?
You all just had a game, right?
你是怎么跟他联系会面的?
How you get a hold of him to parley?
我们一直有联络
We talk now and then.
我呼他
I page his ass.
好
Okay.
你就要这个?
That all you need?
一个号码?
A number?
我能用得上
I make do with it.
还有一个他手下的代号
And a code for one of his peoples.
Wee-Bey用几号 07?
What Wee-Bey use, 07?
"07"
07.
你凭什么认为 我不会就这么收下东西
What makes you think I ain't gonna take this off your hands...
然后把你从这儿扔出去
And throw your ass up outta here?
得了 老兄 等Avon被干掉 那公屋区就重新成为开放市场 对吗
Come on, man, Avon goes down, the projects be open market again, right?
让我想想
Let me understand.
Avon打赌输给我10万
Avon loses $100,000 to me on a bet...
然后你把他的货拿给我
Then you bring me some of his shit...
好让我给你机会追杀他
So that I can put your predatory self on his ass.
他可真不走运 对吧?
Not his day, is it?
靠
Fuck.
我操
Fuck it.
在哪儿?
Where was it?
备胎孔里
The wheel well.
你想起袋子撕破那会儿吗
You remember when the bag broke?
你认为 Daniels会相信吗
Think Daniels will believe it?
你会吗
Would you?
你都不相信我
You didn't believe me.
对不起
I'm sorry.
Savino迟到了 伙计
Savino late, man.
我准备把钱送出 赶快离开这里
I'm ready to make this money-run, get the fuck out here.
你累了
You tired?
我累了 伙计 我饿了
I'm tired, man, I'm hungry.
靠 我也是 想要弄点吃的吗
Shit, me too. Want something to eat from the diner?
行 你要过去吗?
Yeah, you going over there?
给我一份奶酪牛肉三明治 伙计
Get me a cheese steak, man.
- 你也饿了吗 - 是啊 我可以要个汉堡
- You hungry, too? - Yeah, I could do a burger.
好吧 给我在上面加点洋葱
All right. Let me get onions on that, man.
好的
I got you.
你分得对不对?
You organizing it right?
你有把50跟50 100跟100的放一起吗?
You got my $50s with my $50s, and my $100s with my $100s?
好啦 小姐们 晚安
All right, ladies, good night.
我明天准时等你们 听到没
I see you all tomorrow, on time, you hear?
点钱吧 宝贝
Count this money, baby.
咋回事
What the fuck?
是谁
Who's that?
Wee-Bey给我发了个紧急呼叫
Wee-Bey swinging me an emergency call.
靠
Fuck.
还是Bey?
Bey?
911呼叫
911 call.
不行
No.
咱们有规矩 对吗
We got rules, right?
靠
Fuck.
他们有奶酪薯条 我给你弄了些
They had cheese fries, baby. I got you some.
Avon 趴下 伙计 我掩护你
Avon, stay down, man. I got you covered.